shopintimates.com 2011-03-04

# Privacy Policy

At ShopIntimates Singapore, we're committed to our customers' privacy and have made this a high priority. Because of this, we've taken every precaution to eliminate the loss and dissemination of any and all sensitive and personal information. Using the best and most-up-to-date security software on the market, we ensure that customers' transactions and data stay with us. 

First of all, every box we ship is tightly sealed in plain brown paper, and thus tamper-proof, hiding all contents from view. The return address on every postal label, the bill itself **,** and credit card statement all Shows only item order number. We will neither sell, exchange or otherwise benefit from the information a customer provides on the website and will never contact our customers unless directly asked to. An "OPT-IN" prompt allows customers to make this decision for themselves. 

ShopIntimates Singapore does not sell products for purchase by children. We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use Personal Information from children under age 18. If you are under age 18, do not share personal information with us. 

**Retention and Access**

We will take reasonable steps to keep your Personal Information accurate, complete, current, and relevant to its intended use. We keep your Personal Information only as long as we need it for the reasons it was collected. When your Personal Information is no longer required for our purposes, we have procedures to destroy, delete, or erase it.

Any information that ShopIntimates Singapore collects from visitors to this Web Site will be used, stored, or processed, in whole or in part, in Singapore. The principal place in which we hold Personal Information is 170 Upper Bukit Timah Road, #04-39/40 Bukit Timah Shopping Centre, Singapore 588179. All purchases from this Web Site are made in Singapore. 

At your request, we will provide you with reasonable access to your Personal Information, so that you can review what we have stored and, if you choose, request corrections to it. After you request access, we will provide the Personal Information that you request as soon as practically possible and generally no later than 7 days following the request. If you wish to correct your Personal Information, please send us a written explanation of the particular information that you believe should be corrected. Where information will not or cannot be disclosed, we will tell you the reasons for non-disclosure. 

**Security**

Our secure payment website protect your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information that you provide online at our website credit card payment system.

We do not and will not store your credit card in our database. It is discarded the moment your card is authorized. 

**Dispute Resolution**

Please direct any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of Personal Information to us by using the Contact Information given below. We will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Privacy Statement. For complaints that cannot be resolved, we will make available to you an independent dispute resolution process. 

**Contact Information**

In the event of questions about (i) access to your Personal Information, (ii) our collection, use, management, or disclosure of Personal Information, or (iii) this Privacy Statement , contact us at: 

privacy(@)shopintimates.com 

**Privacy Officer : Mabel Chan**

170 Upper Bukit Timah Road, #04-38 Bukit Timah Shopping Centre, Singapore 588179. Singapore ACRA Business Registration No: 53058725D 

Singapore

M-F, 8:30 AM to 5:00 PM (Singapore Time) 

Effective Date 

This Privacy Statement is effective as of JUN 08th , 2009.
